#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ gabrielversoza (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Java
Java Enterprise Edition
JavaScript

#### Certifications

Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 8 Programmer

# **Gabriel Versoza**

Java Developer at Crédit Agricole CIB Singapore

## Summary

A software engineer with more than 5 years of experience in the IT industry. He is involved in designing, building and maintaining monolith to microservices applications. He values clean, well-tested, readable code and loves learning new technologies and its applications to real-world problems.

Specialties: Java and related technologies for web applications

## Experience

Crédit Agricole CIB
Java Developer
February 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Singapore

Cheetah Digital
Senior Software Engineer
October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)

ING
Java Engineer
June 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Finastra 3 years

Software Engineer
December 2017 - May 2018 (6 months)

8/F Zuellig Building, Makati Avenue cor. Paseo de Roxas, Makati City

Associate Software Engineer

June 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 7 months)

8/F Zuellig Building, Makati Avenue cor. Paseo de Roxas, Makati City

**Novare Technologies** 

### Software Engineer Intern

April 2014 - June 2014 (3 months)

7/F Peninsula Court Building, Makati Avenue cor. Paseo de Roxas, Makati City

Develop an application for Automation Testing using Java, Selenium, Apache POI and Maven.

Performs end-to-end testing if needed to ensure the flow of the application.

Participate in modularizing the System Design Documentation.

#### Education

Polytechnic University of the Philippines
Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering (2010 - 2015)